http://www.mystgalaxy.com/policies

Skip to main content
My Account
Staff PicksShop Anti-Racism & Black Voices: A Reading ListLGBTQIA+ Pride readsApparel & AccessoriesBooksAll BooksBy GenreScience FictionFantasyMysteryHorrorYoung Adult Middle Grade & Kids RomanceFairy Tales, Folk Tales, Legends & MythologyLiterary FictionMagical RealismDystopianIndie Next ListIndie Next Kids' ListIndieBound BestsellersUpcoming BooksAudiobookseBooksGift CertificatesPre-orderBusiness & School Bulk OrdersEventsEvent Calendar Year at a GlanceEvent FAQLocal AuthorsVirtual Event Code of ConductSigned BooksCustom Care PackagesBook Clubs & MoreBook SubscriptionBook Discussion GroupYoung Adult Book ClubRomance Book ClubDungeons & Dragons PodcastAboutAbout usPhoto GalleryF.A.Q. COVID -19NewsletterRewards ProgramLocal Book CommunityHolidaysCustom Care PackagesGift CertificatesSigned BooksBookseller BundlesPatreon
Policies
Shipping Policy
Shipping cost is based on the address the items and are sent to, the size, and weight of the items.
In most cases, all orders will be shipped within 1-3 business days.
Book Holds Policy
For all unpaid call-in holds for books we pull from our shelves: Mysterious Galaxy will hold books for 3 days, with no reminder call.
For all unpaid special orders and event books: Mysterious Galaxy will hold books for two weeks, and give one reminder call/ email to the customer, at which point we will hold the book for another 3 days. If we don't hear back from you after this, we will restock/ return your book.
For all paid holds: Mysterious Galaxy will hold your book for 2 weeks, and give frequent reminder calls afterwards. For all paid holds that don't get picked up after 6 months,  Mysterious Galaxy will donate the book to a local charity.
Return Policy
Returns are accepted within 60 days. They must be accompanied by a receipt and be in
condition to enable restocking.
Customers must notify Mysterious Galaxy of any issues with books (damages, missing parcels,etc) within 90 days of purchase.
Privacy Policy: Please click here to read through our Privacy Policy in full.
Information Usage
When you purchase a product from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we
collect your personal information such as your name, address, and email address. When you
browse our store, we automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address. This
information helps us learn about your browser and operating system. With your permission, we
may send you marketing emails about our store, new products and other updates.
Information Usage Consent
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit
card, place an order, arrange for a delivery, or return a purchase, it is implied that you consent to
collection and use of the information provided for that specific reason only. If you previously
provided consent and wish to withdraw your consent, you may contact us to end the continued
collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime. Our contact email is :
mgbooks@mystgalaxy.com
Information Disclosure
We may disclose your personal information if we are required to do so by law.
Third Party Services
Third-party providers will typically collect, use, and disclose your information solely to perform
the services provided to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as those who
provide payment gateways and payment processing, have their own privacy policies in regards to
collecting, using, and disclosing the information that we are required to provide them in order to
complete the purchase-related transaction. For those providers, we recommend that you read
their particular privacy policy in order to understand the manner in which your personal
information will be handled. Also remember that providers follow local jurisdiction, which may
be different from yours or ours. If you choose to proceed with a transaction that involves the
services of a third-party provider, your information may become subject to the jurisdiction’s laws
in which the service provider or its facilities are located. Once you are transferred or leave our
store’s website and/or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer
governed by our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of
other sites and encourage you to read their respective privacy statements.
Security
To protect your personal information, we use industry best practices and standards to make sure
your information is not lost, misused, disclosed, changed, or destroyed. When you provide us
with your credit card information, that information is encrypted using secure socket layer
technology (SSL) and stored with AES-256 encryption. Please note that no method of
transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, but we follow all industry standards in order to
minimize and prevent fraudulent activity.
Privacy Policy Changes
We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy at any time. Changes and/or clarifications will
take immediate effect if posted on the website. If we make material changes to the policy, we
will notify you of the update. If our store is acquired by or merged with another company, your
information may be transmitted to the new company/owners.
Virtual Event - Scholastic Presents I Read YA @ Home!
12/14/2020 - 5:00pm
Virtual Event - Max and Glen Keane discussing Trash Truck and Over the Moon
12/15/2020 - 7:00pm
Virtual Event - Sara Foster discussing The Hidden Hours
12/16/2020 - 7:00pm
more
